Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
- Nicholas Bell.
- Mr. Campano.
In person.
You're my hero.
Just doing my job.
Sure.
But I'm guessing if my associate.
Mr. Grey. drew any other public defender.
he'd be sitting in jail right now.
That may be true.
Cigar?
Before lunch?
There's no such thing
as a bad time for a good cigar.
Save it for later.
Consider it a signing bonus.
I haven't signed anything.
- Have I?
- Not yet.
So. tell me. why are you leaving
the public defender's office?
I haven't decided to leave yet.
But I just had another kid.
That's what I figured.
Is this a job offer?
No.
But I understand you have one
from a prestigious. white-shoe
criminal defense firm in Houston.
Those are all the clients
you'll be expected to defend there.
Corporations destroying the environment.
banks stealing from retirement funds
and a whole cadre of rich sociopaths
facing charges for everything
from extortion to murder.
I'll pay you double.
You can stay here in Austin.
I'll just be a...
another client.
If you're going to work for criminals.
Mr. Bell.
you might as well
work for the generous ones.
Pick your poison.
Mmm.
Don't have anything stronger?
Not for 75-year-olds with heart conditions
who've just come back from the dead.
It's got a lot of sugar.
Might wanna take it easy.
I'm gonna toss you right off this plane.
Ah.
Just when I was starting to
get used to it.
Yeah. that's the problem.
Getting used to it.
Makes it hard to stop.
This wasn't your fault.
What if I'd said no to Frank?
Kept flying coach.
Maybe things would've been different.
Maybe.
I need to make this right.
I owe that to you.
To all of you.
Then we will.
Why on earth would they go to Paris?
We don't even know where to meet them.
Then we'll have to wait till they tell us.
That's not very fun. is it?
You're not worried?
I am.
But at the moment.
we're traveling with five million dollars
Teddy Campano owes to
an international drug cartel.
so it's not at the very top of my list.
Look. I'm concerned about Bailey too.
of course.
But I trust Nicholas.
You do?
Yeah. he loves Bailey as much as you do.
You see eye-to-eye on that.
He'd never put her in harm's way.
And he could be helpful with Frank.
Well. that part might be complicated.
You mean if Quinn's involved?
Teddy's always been rash.
but Quinn's smart.
- Mmm.
- Frank adores her.
If Quinn's involved...
Yeah.
So a question. Ms. Favreau.
Why France?
Why not London.
the financial capital of Europe?
Uh... It was time for my business to expand.
And it felt like
the perfect way to honor my mother.
Oh! Is she from Paris?
No. but she was from Èze. on the coast.
And as there no banks
available to buy there...
No. they deal more in perfumes.
How the fuck
do you lose five million dollars?
Did I fucking say I lost it?
Whoever switched the RFID on the can
must've taken it...
I don't wanna know. I don't wanna know.
- Oh. right. Saint Quinn.
- Fuck you.
If the syndicate doesn't get their money
they're gonna come after all of us.
What do you want from me. Teddy?
Well. right now. I could use a loan.
I don't have that kinda cash.
- You own a bank.
- Yeah. which has to stay legitimate.
So where the fuck am I gonna
come up with this money?
- Talk to Dad?
- He'll lose his shit.
He has the money.
It's better he hears it from you.
You gonna rat me out?
Not me.
I assume the syndicate
decided to work with you
because they thought you had
Dad's backing.
So. if you are not holding up
your side of the deal...
Quinnie. he'll kill me.
He's pretty used to your fuckups
at this point.
I have to get back to my interview.
Just talk to Dad.
Please try not to screw up again. okay?
Not exactly how I thought
I'd first see Paris.
Pretty spectacular though. huh?
Your grandmother. she preferred Tuscany.
Where her family was from.
I was always drawn here.
I'd drag your mother to the Louvre.
Just trying to give her what I never had.
She humored me.
She never loved Paris the way I did.
But your father...
He took Hannah here for their honeymoon.
Ah. she told me.
The Victoria Palace.
The best hotel in the world.
Hmm.
And small. discreet.
Only 60 keys.
That's where we're staying?
Figured it'd be an easy rendezvous.
Uh... Also. Frank.
he likes to stay at Hôtel Lumineux.
the hoity-toity five-star down the street.
You're gonna wait. right?
You're not gonna approach him
until we've discussed it with Hannah.
Not directly. no.
No. he doesn't love surprises.
Neither do we.
Waiting to greet me.
I feel like royalty.
I'm just happy we're all here.
Yeah. okay. okay.
I'm turning 80. I'm not dying.
At least not yet.
Quinnie here?
She's just finishing up an interview
with some fancy business rag.
Which is just as well. We can. uh. chat.
Why? Is there something wrong?
No. just a few things to discuss.
I have some fresh Behikes.
Come on. Pop.
You know I can't do
your weird morning cigar thing.
Oh. shit. I gotta take this.
I'll be right back.
- Hello?
- Mr. Campano.
One of our friends
at the Marseille train station
ID'd a couple on the 7:01 to Paris.
You're sure it's them?
He seemed fairly certain.
When does the train get there?
On time arrival at Gare de Lyon
30 minutes from now.
Text me the info.
I need men at the Gare de Lyon. now.
Ah. it could be worse.
We're in Paris.
- Hmm. It's almost romantic.
- Almost.
Hang on. My phone.
Ah.
I can think of worse places to hide out.
Wait.
They'll have men all over the station
looking for us.
Let's find some cover.
We have eight-year-old twins.
but I remember those days.
Shh.
Here. let us help you out.
- Thank you.
- Yes.
Merci.
Hey.
Are we sure they were on the train?
That's what we were told...
Wait. I think I see them.
How did you miss them?
No. I don't give a shit how you do it.
I need you to find them!
Hi. Dad.
Quinnie.
Hi.
How's my girl?
- Oh. I'm good.
- Yeah?
Busy with the acquisition.
but I'm glad you came.
Are you sure about that?
Yes.
It's gonna be nice.
the three of us celebrating your birthday.
Any idea what's going on there?
You know Teddy. always
lighting fires for himself to put out.
Yeah.
Oh. Shoot. Sorry. I need to take this.
- I'll catch up with you later?
- All right.
Love you.
Welcome. Mr. Bell.
- We have the room you requested.
- Mmm.
Can I take you to it?
Oh.
Why don't you let Ms. Gachon
show you the room?
How about Paris?
We can all go.
You have not lived
until you've smoked a cigar
in the lounge at the Hôtel Lumineux.
Is that right?
We can take the kids
for a hot chocolate tasting.
Jenny loves that.
Loved that.
You need another drink.
What a fucking month!
First Jenny.
now this New York bullshit.
They're ticky-tack charges.
Bobby can handle it.
Bobby looks good in a sharkskin suit.
But he's no Nicky Bell.
I won't do what Bobby does.
I'm of no use to you if I get disbarred.
I won't cross that line.
Who's asking you to?
Nicholas.
Thank God.
Where's Bailey?
- Hi.
Bails.
Hey. Dad.
- It's not safe for...
- It's not safe for me to be here.
Yes. I know.
Well. for either of you. What's going on?
Why are you here?
Maybe we should all sit down.
I went through this after Kate died.
but I...
I knew Ivan was a friend. but I...
But you didn't know
he'd become a prosecutor.
- I should've listened to her.
- You and me both.
I just... I couldn't hear it.
And I couldn't...
I just couldn't hold back.
I couldn't pull away from Frank.
My mom knew that. and so she decided
to take matters into her own hands.
And you think they killed her.
All the privileged information
I had in my files.
if the Feds had been able to
get at that through Kate.
it could've toppled
the Campanos' entire organization.
So Frank did do this.
No.
No. he wouldn't have.
No. I'm sure of it.
Teddy.
Yes. I know you've been very generous.
Yes. I know...
But I can make a partial delivery...
I understand that's not
what Mr. Perec and I agreed to.
but if I could speak with him...
Look. I'm gonna get you
your fucking money.
I just need a minute. okay?
Are you still into Valium
or have you moved on
to something stronger?
It's just Ativan.
but thanks for the concern.
What are you doing?
Leave me alone. I've got it handled.
It doesn't seem like it.
You wanna take over?
You wanna run the show?
I am just trying to help.
You wanna be helpful.
find me a fucking loan.
I did.
Just talk to him.
Hey.
Are you okay?
Mmm.
If I'd only walked away when I
realized what Nicholas was doing...
Kate told me. I...
I just argued.
This is my fault.
- You were young.
- Yeah.
And Nicholas was larger than life.
It was an impossible situation.
I don't know what I would've done.
But I certainly don't think
anyone is to blame.
Or at least. not anyone here.
That's generous.
I love you.
Oh. Oh. hey. Hey. hey. hey.
I'm trying to work my way up
to an apology here.
To my dad?
Your dad. you. Charlie.
It's a long list.
Oh. I don't deserve you.
Probably not.
- We got a plan.
- Yeah.
- So do we.
- Mmm.
I thought
they were shipping drugs.
We think maybe Teddy's not
shipping drugs for the syndicate.
We think he's laundering their money.
The money could be a bargaining chip.
We could make a deal for all of us.
We wanna go directly to Teddy and Quinn.
Quinn?
We think Quinn might be involved.
She was Teddy's first phone call
when the money went missing.
So she was lying to us?
She was lying to me?
Well. it sounded complicated.
She seemed so sincere when
she was talking about my mom.
Well. she was close with Kate.
She wasn't lying about that.
It's not the worst thing
if Quinn is involved.
She's more rational than Teddy.
That's not saying much.
And even if she makes a deal. Teddy'll
break it as soon as he's in the clear.
She won't be able to stop that.
So you. you still wanna go to Frank.
Well. Frank has been
listening to my counsel for 40 years.
Going to Frank with what we know now.
I might get to the truth
of what happened to Kate.
And that's the closest we're
ever gonna get to justice for her.
Are you willing to let that go?
Either of you?
After Kate died...
I was obsessed with
getting justice for her.
But now...
...the important thing is us being together.
I...
I wanna know what happened to her.
more than anything.
I've been living with
half-truths about her my whole life.
I think our safety has to be the priority.
And if there's a chance
we can all be together.
Okay.
Okay. we do it your way.
What's the plan?
How are you gonna get to Quinn and Teddy?
Mmm.
Hell. it's noon somewhere.
That's more like it.
I've got one.
"At college.
study well and be like a cleanser.
Work fast and leave no rings."
- Did I give that to you?
- Mmm.
- That's awful.
- Really?
I always thought it was good advice.
Speaking of which. I could use some. uh...
Sorry. Pop.
I'm gonna have to take a rain check.
We'll smoke them later. yeah?
Sure.
Did he talk to you?
No.
I'm gonna have to step in
before he gets us all killed.
If you do that he'll lose
the respect of the syndicate.
Maybe it's time
to put someone else in charge.
You know I don't want that.
And I've never wanted it for you.
But we're running out of options.
It's a lot. huh?
Yeah.
But at least it all makes sense now.
And she wasn't just a victim.
She was brave and strong
and trying to protect her family.
Just like her daughter.
I'm sorry.
You are? For what?
I was so skeptical of
what you guys were doing.
I... I feel bad that I doubted you and Dad.
Well. you should.
Who ever heard of
a 20-something doubting their parents?
Bails? What is it?
You having second thoughts?
No.
Just be careful.
- Yeah.
- Okay?
Both of you.
We will.
Okay. Promise.
Keep an eye on him.
Use the burner if you need us.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
Daddy.
- Daddy.
- Yes. Katie?
Don't you want some hot chocolate?
Bring me some back.
Tell Quinnie to bring me one too.
Katie. I love you all the world.
I love you too.
I told it would be a celebration.
I should've gotten you off.
You're being too hard on yourself.
It's only six months.
That's a win for the good guys.
When I get out.
we'll come back here for longer.
And we'll go to Èze.
It's on the riviera.
There's a hike there
the octogenarians swear by.
You think we'll make it to 80?
That's my point.
They walk it every day.
They swear it keeps them young.
It's called Nietzsche's Path.
Very French.
I'm going to need
someone to visit me in prison.
I'm going to need to get information.
I'm going to need to
pass along certain orders.
You should ask Lane to do that.
If Lane comes. every FBI agent
in Texas will be listening in.
But if it's you...
Abusing attorney client privilege
is against the law.
You know that.
I know I need to keep control
of my organization.
You've never asked me for this.
No. I hardly ever ask anyone to
cross that line for me personally.
It requires a deep level of trust.
I'm flattered.
You should be.
Nietzsche said what is done for love
always occurs beyond good and evil.
You stay here.
I want you on Bailey.
I see him.
He's outside the watch store.
He has two guards with him.
Copy.
Let me see what I can do about that.
Stay out here.
He went inside. Sweating.
Good.
Yeah. but the guards are still there.
We need to get him alone.
Another coffee. Ma'am?
Yes. thank you.
- Bonjour. madame.
- Merci.
What are we looking for today?
I don't know...
Let me see something large. masculine...
what someone older would wear.
Of course!
Would you like some tea? A coffee?
No. no... Just the watch.
A glass of champagne. perhaps?
No. no... Actually. yeah. Thanks.
You following me?
More like babysitting.
Don't think buying a $50.000 watch
makes up for losing five million.
It's a present for Dad.
If you live long enough to give it to him.
What are you doing here?
Taking over.
Temporarily.
Fixing your mess so it doesn't
lead to something more permanent.
You talked to Dad?
Damn right I talked to Dad.
I told you this was my thing.
- I told you I didn't want Dad involved.
- I know.
But I couldn't watch you
self-destruct again.
Your champagne. sir.
He'll need one too.
Is he still inside?
Yeah.
Why would he ignore Perec?
You think he has any idea?
Maybe you should get out of there.
We agreed this is our best play.
Sure. but...
If he's made you...
Well. then what? We still have his money.
I think he's just afraid.
Just send him another text.
See if you can speed him along.
No. I don't like it.
Well. you don't have to like it.
You just have to trust me.
Your champagne.
- I'll have another.
- Yes. sir. One moment please.
So. Dad gave you the money?
Of course not. He's livid.
He's not gonna give you that kinda cash.
How the fuck does that help me?
He spoke with Perec.
He said he smoothed things over.
You don't smooth things over
with these people.
That's not how it works.
He's been doing this
a lot longer than you have.
- I think he knows how it works.
- You're wrong.
Dad was never in this league.
And unless you can magically
make five million dollars appear
by end of day. we're all fucked.
He's watching you?
That doesn't make any sense.
I was there when Dad spoke to him.
It sounded like...
Yeah. I changed my mind.
We're not gonna be buying.
Dad would love that one.
Buy the watch.
Go back to the hotel.
Quinn. you don't know these people.
Actually. I do.
Anything?
Let's go.
Yeah. he's leaving.
Looks like he's going back
the way he came.
Do you think I should follow?
Let's take a walk.
Housekeeping.
- Oh. Could you come back later. please?
- No problem.
Grandpa?
Where is he?
I don't know.
He didn't say.
- To Nietzsche.
Wait until we get to Èze.
Have I mentioned the restaurant?
Prince of Monaco eats there
every other week.
Then I hope you're paying.
I know I don't need to say it again.
but. um. you deserve to hear it.
What you did. I'll never forget it.
Anything you ever need from me. any favor.
it's yours.
Long way to come for a cigar.
I'm told you haven't lived until you've
smoked a cigar in Hôtel Lumineux.
Hey.
- You're not surprised to see me.
- No. I'm not.
For someone who claims
not to have anything to do with
your father's business.
you certainly seem to be involved.
I told you. the only way this ends well
is if you let your husband go.
My husband is not to blame here.
He has five million dollars
of my family's money.
Your family killed his wife.
I know he believes that.
but there is simply no basis for it.
Did you know Kate spoke with a US attorney
about Nicholas's work with your dad
just before she died?
Yes.
Bailey told me that.
And I told her that she is
looking for answers where there are none.
Right. You've been
completely transparent with her.
I've made real efforts with Bailey.
If my brother killed her mother.
I'd make real efforts too.
Teddy didn't have the brains
or the wherewithal back then
to do anything even remotely like this.
I don't know.
He's pretty good at making a mess.
Kate was my friend.
and it was a difficult thing to get past.
but this has nothing to do
with the matter at hand.
But doesn't it?
Everything.
It all started with Kate's death.
Owen never would've gone after Nicholas
or your family
if Kate hadn't died.
If she. if she hadn't been killed.
You and your father have
the opportunity to make this right.
You have no proof
of Teddy's involvement.
Oh. come on. Frank.
Look what he's been up to now.
I don't know.
Yeah. okay.
And I still can't believe that Katie
was talking to the federal prosecutor.
What was she thinking?
Well. she was concerned about Ethan.
And she was right.
I shouldn't have involved him
in our business.
So. this was on you.
Yeah. it's on me.
I was in denial about
the risks of being in your orbit.
Bullshit.
You were fully aware of what you were
signing on for the first time we met.
And only a fool would think
that the private planes. the Cohibas.
came without a price.
Maybe.
And maybe I should've anticipated
just how dear that price would be.
But I suppose I trusted you to protect me.
Hmm. Yeah.
At the very least. to protect my family.
What do you want from me. Nicky?
I can't give you your daughter back.
No. No. you can't. No.
But you can give back
something to my granddaughter.
You can give her back her father.
You are focusing on the wrong things.
Dredging up the past
isn't going to change the present.
You need to give my brother the money.
Yeah.
I'm trying to make a deal here.
You're in no position to bargain.
No? Teddy's in bed
with some pretty scary people.
Teddy is scary people.
And you need to give the money back
before you get hurt.
Sounds like a threat.
It's just the truth.
Why are you here?
I'm here because we didn't
trust Teddy to control himself.
"We."
You are involved.
Of course the...
the amount of money that Teddy's
laundering. a bank would come in handy.
I don't have to listen to this.
How long have you been involved?
Has it been this whole time?
You've got a lot of nerve.
Which is good.
You're gonna need it.
That money's to be back in our hands
by the end of the day.
Or what?
What could you possibly do to us
that you haven't done already?
Me?
I haven't done anything to you. Hannah.
But I wouldn't try me.
I'm not the soft touch my brother is.
Yes. keep your eyes on her
after my sister leaves...
We follow her. and... exactly.
That asshole can't be far.
You're putting me in a terrible position.
Yeah. You'd have to reassert
control over the organization.
I'm in control of the organization.
Oh. yeah? I thought Teddy was
running the show now. the past year or so.
Fuck you.
It's my business.
Mm-mmm. Not what I've heard.
You calling me weak?
No. I'm calling you old.
I don't care how long I've known you.
I will put you in the fucking ground.
Right.
Finish the job that your son started.
Go ahead.
But it won't solve your problem.
Frank. it's time to step in.
For my sake. and for yours.
Do you know how much
effort that would take?
Yeah. I am old and so are you.
We don't have the stamina we used to.
It's nothing a hike in Èze couldn't cure.
"Anything you ever need.
Any favor."
Isn't that what you said to me?
I can't do this alone.
Who's asking you to?
Haven't I always been there?
- Hmm?
- Yeah.
So. come on. Let's get back in there. huh?
We'll clean up Teddy's mess. all right?
We'll get you a proper successor.
And we'll get you and your children out
of this nasty business once and for all.
You know the town motto of Èze?
Hmm?
"In death I am reborn."
- You think Quinn's in charge?
- I don't know.
But she's definitely deep in this.
- And she's smart.
- Smarter than Teddy. that's for sure.
Bailey's at Hôtel Lumineux?
We gotta go.
Yeah.
Owen.
Yes. Bring them to the docks.
I'll take it from there.
Mr. Campano.
Do I know you?
No. but you knew my mother.
What the fuck are you doing here?
I came to talk to you
and your father about the money.
I have a-a birthday dinner
with Teddy and Quinn at L'ambroisie.
If you're still around.
maybe we could start work in the morning.
I'm not going anywhere.
What?
Wait. Wait.
Hey!
- We need to split up.
- Yeah. down below.
I'll get to Bailey.
You're not going anywhere until you
tell me where the fuck your father is.
Let me go.
Get your hands off her.
- What the fuck?
- Get your fucking hands off of her!
- You're not supposed to be here.
- Let her go. son.
Now.
You knew he was alive
and you didn't fucking tell me?
Because I wanted to keep him alive.
- I had nothing to do with it.
- Hmm?
No. don't look at me like that.
I'm not the problem here.
He's the problem.
him and his whole fucking family.
You're wrong.
You don't know what you're doing. Teddy.
- You never have.
- You gonna listen to him?
He's your lawyer.
He's more than that.
Always has been.
If you had any sense.
you'd understand that.
But it doesn't matter.
You're no longer in charge.
No. No.
It's over. son.
It's over.
Hey! Hey!
Leave them alone.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Okay.
- Bailey.
- Everything's fine.
What happened?
Pop. you don't know
what the hell you're doing.
This is a huge fucking mistake.
Did you kill Nicholas's daughter?
- What?
- Did you kill Katie?
Kate Smith?
No.
Just like you didn't try to murder
Nicholas. or get us in bed with Perec.
Dad. I don't know
what he's been telling you.
- but you...
- Listen!
I love you.
You'll always be my boy.
- Monsieur Campano.
- Yeah?
Teddy Campano.
Yeah? What's it to you?
Get down!
Security!
I need security now!
All right. We're right here. Frank.
Frank. Frank. we're right here.
All right. help is coming.
We're right here. We're right here.
Dad! Daddy! Daddy!
Dad.
He's gone.
Quinnie. he's gone.
What the fuck have you done?
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm